Hello everyone!
I'm Kirari Ochiai from not.equal ME!
I'm Natsuna Kawaguchi.
I'm Miho Sakurai.
Hello! So, this time
7-Eleven Uncle Bread General Election!
Yay!
Yes! I know that convenience stores carry breads made by various manufacturers
But this time, I'd like to focus on 7-Eleven's original bread
I'm going to make a general election for 7-Eleven's original breads.
It's the best!
I've been waiting for this! This is the kind of project I've been waiting for!
I know, right!
Look at this! I'm getting such a heightened awareness of this!
It's fun!
It's bread!
I've taken the Pansilv certification
I've taken a bread certification called "Pansilb Certification", so I'd like to share with you all
I'm hoping to share the deliciousness of 7-Eleven's bread with you all today.
I'm hoping that I can tell you how delicious 7-Eleven's bread is today, while I'm campaigning for the election.
So please come hungry!
This time, each of you has 5 points.
For example, 2 points for this bread, 1 point for this bread, 3 points for that bread, and so on.
We'll give you points.
And with that statistic, we will decide the total statistics for all of us.
You mean the total for all of us?
Yes, that's right.
I see.
Now, the points of Momokyu.
First of all!
Yes!
Two points!
Oh!
One at a time!
Yeah!
Two of these!
Oh!
I'd like to give it to you!
First of all!
Oh!
Aged French Charred Garlic and Butter
Nice voice! Good voice!
And!
Buttercream Camekopa!
Mm-hm-hm!
Yes, yes, yes!
For these two!
Oh!
Two points!
This Camecopa?
Yeah!
Bread flavor?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
It was so good and the cream was butter cream!
And the cream, butter cream!
Yeah!
It was so good.
It was sweet and delicious.
Aah!
It's just like Momo Kyu, isn't it?
Yes!
One point left!
This one!
Oh!
Corn mayonnaise!
It's a classic!
I just had this for the first time.
Oh!
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It's delicious.
Yeah!
I just thought it would cheer you up.
Great!
Yes!
Cheer up!
How about you, Nocchan?
Yes!
My first two points!
Oh!
Two points!
Yeah!
Over here.
Oh!
It's very popular!
Yes!
Buttercream rice kofta.
Oh!
It's in there.
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes!
The reason is the gentle taste
It's so good that anyone would say it's delicious!
Yes!
It was delicious.
It really is!
It's good for everyone!
Yeah!
Two points here!
And!
Next is one point!
Oh!
First!
This way!
Oh!
Mayonnaise roll
This way!
Mayonnaise lovers!
I absolutely love mayonnaise!
Yes!
The taste of mayonnaise really spread in my mouth and it was delicious!
And!
Here is another one!
Oh!
That's it!
Chibi Chibi Corn Mayonnaise
Oh!
It's mayonnaise!
Mayonnaise!
Some mayonnaise!
Yes!
And!
One more point!
Here!
Torn bread!
This is it!
Just like 7-Eleven!
That's right!
I often eat this bread in the morning.
The balance is just right!
I know!
So I love it already!
That's all!
That's all I have to say.
Oh!
A fan.
Fan Leader
The fans would like to announce!
Please!
Yes!
Oh!
I was really worried!
Yeah!
You're in trouble!
But aren't there a few points?
Aah!
I think so.
You're right!
That's right!
Well, let's start with one point!
Oh!
This one!
That's it!
Oh!
I would like to give 1 point to the Aged French Charred Garlic & Butter!
The aroma of the garlic when you open it was really good, and I think most people would probably go to a convenience store and eat it right away!
I think most people go to a convenience store and eat it right then and there!
I always rebake it at home.
I always rebake it at home, but I wanted to give it a point for being so tasty without rebaking.
From the top!
They are all great pansierge!
I mean, 1 point for that!
Then one point for the next one!
Oh!
I'm torn... I'm torn...
I'm struggling, I'm struggling, I'm struggling, I'm struggling...
Yes!
This way!
Look at that!
Raisin custard!
I used to eat this a lot when I was a student.
That's right.
I used to eat it this way.
What?
Do you see it? You see this little layer here?
You peel it off and eat it one by one.
Don't nibble on it.
Peel it off.
Here.
It's delicious when you peel it off, isn't it?
So, I'll give you one point for this.
I want you to peel it off and eat it, too.
By the way, there is a product similar to this called butterscotch.
It tastes good when you peel it off, too.
That's right.
It's delicious too!
A tip for you!
Here's a tip for you!
Followed by
Durun.
Oh my!
I recommended it.
Well, you can't miss this one.
The best part is...
This way, this way.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, no.
You can do this?
7-Eleven's
Everyone is Masiko.
I'm really struck by it.
I see what you mean.
I was hoping that they would release a variety of cream versions of this.
Even soybean flour cream!
It's absolutely delicious!
I'd like to see them come out with a variety of creams.
I'll keep that in mind.
In the U.S.A.
In America.
We'll do it in America.
One point for peace.
And...
You just announced three points.
Yes, sir.
I'll give you the remaining 2 points.
I would like to announce
I'd like to announce
What?
Oh.
Oh!
The product I'm interested in is after the commercial.
Can I buy ads? Can I buy ads if I'm a member of Filtarm? Yes, they don't.
Yes, so please announce it as soon as possible.
This way.
Butter cream rice-flour bread.
I was wondering if it's possible to make rice-flour bread this doughy without going to a bakery.
I've been buying rice-flour bread at bakeries lately, and I'm really impressed.
As Momo said earlier, the butter cream is really good, and the glutinousness blends well with the bread.
I melted the buttercream in my mouth.
I'm going to slap it.
It's very, very good, so I'm going to give you two points for that.
The best!
So that's my general election!
But everyone's pretty good. I'm wearing something. I feel like I could have played a little.
I wonder what happened, but I have a feeling it's Kim's. Yes, you're right.
So, the point totals are done.
I'm curious about the result...
Yes, I'm curious about the result.
Yes, I'm curious about the result...
I'd like to announce the results, starting with the third place winner.
The third place winner is the same as the first place winner.
The third place went to the bread with corn mayonnaise and chocolate cream.
I think it's the regular version.
Yes, the regular version too.
I also like the thinness of the corn mayonnaise bread.
Good. And that's a good point.
Yes, sir.
It's a little bit... if you're looking at it right now at 7-Eleven, you're probably thinking...
Yes. Yes.
And that brings us to number two.
Aged French Charred Garlic and Butter.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
It's so good!
I can already tell by looking at it that it's delicious!
7-Eleven has really made the right decision!
If you like garlic, you should definitely try this!
And...
And finally...
Finally!
JEJE!
Butter cream rice flour bread
Wow!
This is the best of the best!
By the way
This butter cream rice flour bread
It's only sold in Shibuya Ward and Akita Prefecture!
That's right!
This bread dough contains 30% rice flour produced in Akita Prefecture!
I see!
That's right.
That's right, Akita is all about rice!
That's why you wanted it.
The power of Akita!
So, if you think you would like to have it
Please give it to Shibuya Ward or Akita Prefecture!
We are waiting for you in the east!
outing!
Yes, that's why we have announced our general election for our guess bread!
Ha!
We'd love to hear about your favorite bread, so please write a lot in the comments section!
That's all for now! Noble & Mii!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!